<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ASHA Nepal Project</title>
    <link>http://asha-np.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ASHA Nepal Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://asha-np.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>About &#34;ASHA Nepal Project&#34;</title>
      <link>http://asha-np.org/services/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://asha-np.org/services/about/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ASHA Nepal Project&lt;/strong&gt; aims to improve public health and mental care in rural areas of Nepal with IT.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of our team members went to Nepal and conducted a health camp just after the April-May 2015 Nepal earthquake and found a lack of patient information management and sustainable health support. After that, we launched this project to address these problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our team consists of medical staffs such as doctors and nurses as well as engineers. We are developing an useful software application to manage and share patient information efficiently and to provide sustainable health support.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What we do</title>
      <link>http://asha-np.org/services/what-we-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://asha-np.org/services/what-we-do/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are developing a patient information management system, named &amp;ldquo;ASHA fusion&amp;rdquo;, which can be easily used by medical staffs in rural areas of Nepal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have conducted trials in a hospital and a health camp with supports of local partners in order to introduce our software into practice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, we expect our software to become even more helpful to improve public health by collecting a lot of information and extracting insights from it.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project</title>
      <link>http://asha-np.org/services/project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://asha-np.org/services/project/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;trial:10be9c81b9315bdc8704629d17642664&#34;&gt;Trial&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In March 2016, our team went to Nepal and conducted a health camp using the first version of our software &amp;ldquo;ASHA fusion&amp;rdquo; with supports of local NGOs and doctors. Local doctors and nurses used ASHA fusion and gave us lots of feedback with positive feelings.
Furthermore, we tried to introduce ASHA fusion to the hospital operation.
Furthermore, we implemented trial use at a private hospital, and discussed introducing ASHA fusion to hospital operations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;future:10be9c81b9315bdc8704629d17642664&#34;&gt;Future&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our team started to develop more convenient system based on the feedback from the users.
We are going to continue to improve our system and to spread it to health camps and hospitals by visiting there continuously.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>